<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Namaz Alert</string>
    <string name="channel_name">chanel_name</string>
    <string name="fajar">Fajar:</string>

    <!-- OLD ID's -->
    <!--<string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-2137792542799325~6269926192</string>
    <string name="admob_banner_id">ca-app-pub-2137792542799325/8764776338</string>-->
    <string name="admob_interstitial">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>


    <!-- NEW ID's -->
    <string name="admob_app_id">ca-app-pub-4677462554197877~8699663585</string>
    <string name="admob_banner_id">ca-app-pub-4677462554197877/1942683543</string>
    <string name="about">

The most authentic Islamic App for Namaz Timing, accurate Zakaat Calculator, e-Tasbeeh, Qibla Compass, and 99 names of Allah SWT.

Stay on top of your Namaz, the best Islamic app to get accurate Namaz Times, Depending on the Current Location, the Namaz times will be saved, and as soon as it is saved, the alarm will be set and at the time of alarm, the call of Namaz will be played and notification will come.

eTasbih- Very convenient for everyday uses of Muslims to pray and make tesbihat, zikar after Namaz.
This is counter-tasbih, through which you can set the target. when you reach your target, you will be notified by Vibration.

Zakaat Calculator is an option that helps Muslims around the world to calculate their Zakaat. The main purpose of the Zakaat Calculator is to enable Muslims to find out how much Zakat they have to pay after deducting their liabilities and personal requirements from the total.

Qibla Compass is an option to Finder Compass, Shows 100% accurate Qibla Direction worldwide
Qibla finder app is a GPS compass that helps Muslims to find Qibla direction from anywhere in the world. Qibla compass is using your current location with the help of a GPS map to find out accurate Qibla direction

99 Names of Allah is an option that has been produced to let Muslims all over the world get familiar with the 99 Beautiful Names of Allah SWT (Asma Ul Husna)
You can listen and read the 99 names of Allah through audio play and at the same time the pictures of the names will be changing and the meaning in Urdu will be appearing.

This App is developed by Gexton INC.</string>

</resources>
